现在我还记得很多
Now I remember a lot of stories from back in the days
遇见你妈妈之前的事情
before I met your mother.
但有一个故事我是不记得的
But there's one story I don't remember.
Marshall叔叔一直
Uncle Marshall still refers to
把它称为菠萝事件
it as "the pineapple incident."
那个晚上和平时没两样
The night started like any other.
我们在楼下的酒吧
We were downstairs at the bar.
我请的
Hey, it's on the house.
是我自己调的
it's my own concoction.
我叫它红龙
I call it the red dragon.
谢谢! 这太好了
All: Thanks! That was really sweet.
我们不是真的要尝吧, 是不?
We're not really doing shots,are we?
我可不想\n别, 别, 别
I hope not. No,no,no.
这些看起来象血
these look kind of like blood.
好了, 我知道你们以前\n否决过这个猜想
Okay,I know that you've \nall dismissed this theory before.
但Carl有可能是吸血鬼吗?
But is there any chance that Carl is a vampire?
不, 伙计们, 我是认真的\n想想有没可能
no,you guys,I'm serious.Think about it.
他总是穿黑色的衣服
He always wears black.
我们从来没在白天\n见过他, 只有傍晚后
We never see him in the daylight,only after dark.
噢, 天那
Oh,my god.
确实形容的象吸血鬼...\n或者, 你们知道, 是酒吧调酒师
That does describe a vampire... \nor,you know,a bartender.
我得去打扮了
Well, I should go get dressed.
你要去哪, 伙计? 约会?
Where you going,buddy?Hot date?
我来说, 她要和一个\n身家数十亿的富翁约会
I'll say.She's going out with a billionaire.
我说了不要那样称呼他
I told you not to call him that.
等等, 你真要和\n身家数十亿的富翁约会?
Wait,you're really going out with a billionaire?
他不是身家数十亿
He's not a billionaire.
他是身家数亿
He's a hundred-millionaire.
为什么人们总是分不清楚呢?
Why do people always round up?
那么, 呃\nThurston Howell要带你去哪?
So,uh,where's Thurston Howell taking you?
一个慈善晚会
A charity dinner.
对, 2,000块一个盘子
Yeah,$2,000 a plate.
是1,500 别再弄错了
$1,500. Stop rounding up.
是为第三世界的饥民办的
And it's for third world hunger.
你要献身吗?
You gonna put out?
什么? 只有一个原因
What?There's only one reason
他才会带她去那个晚会
he's taking her to this dinner,
而且这绝不是因为小富翁
and it's not so little Mu Tu
需要人服侍喝疟疾药
can get his malaria pills.
刚才我的灵魂呕吐了
I think my soul just threw up a little bit.
嗯, 我要迟到了
Well,I'm gonna be late.
你们玩的开心点
You guys have fun.
- 拜 回头见\n- 拜 回头见
-Bye. See ya. \n-Bye.See ya.
你还好吧?
You okay?
当然 为什么这么问?
Sure. Why?
噢, 我不知道
Oh,I don't know.
你的梦中情人和一个\n身家数十亿的富翁约会
Girl of your dreams dating a billionaire.
好吧, 首先, 他身家数亿
Okay,first of all,hundred-millionaire.
其次 她不是我的梦中情人
And second,she's not the girl of my dream.
我们只是朋友
we're just friends.
听着, 如果我们在一起\n是不明智的
Look,it would not be smart if we got together.
我是说, 我希望一切安定下来
I mean,I'm looking to settle down,
她希望的是...
she's looking for...
什么?你说完了? 太好了
wha...? You done? Great.
看那边4号桌
Check out table number four.
看到最后那个小辣妹了吗?
See that little hottie on the end?
她有点矮, 但胸够大
She's short,but has an ample bosom.
我喜欢  她就象个半个乳房
I love it. She's,like,half boob.
我们过去
Let's go.
嗯, 然后说什么?
Yeah,and say what?
我们的开场白是什么?
What's our big opening line?
我... 呃... 爹地回家了
I... uh... daddy's home.
爹地回家了?
Daddy's home?
对
Yeah.
好吧, 你希望我们现在过去
Okay,you want us to go over there right now
然后跟那些女生说\n"爹地回家了"?
and say to those girls,"daddy's home"?
认真想清楚点, Barney
Really think about that,Barney.
嗯 耶, 我觉得很不错
Hmm. Yeah,I think it's pretty solid.
好吧, 想下这个
Okay,think about this.
菜单里有任何
Is there even a single item
放了大蒜的菜吗?
on the menu that has garlic in it?
大蒜炸薯条
Garlic fries.
好吧, 嗯, 我再想想
Okay,well,I'll get back to you.
噢, 爹地回来了
Oh,daddy's back.
看吧, 如果你有认真想想...
See,if you'd taken a moment to think about that...
那么爹地就不可能拿到
then daddy wouldn't have gotten this
这个7位数的父亲节卡片了\n……来自于Amy的
seven-digit father's day card from Amy.
啊 那管用吗?
Ah. That worked?
我恨这个世界
I hate the world.
Ted, 你的问题是每次\n做什么都是考虑, 考虑, 考虑
Ted,your problem is \nall you do is think,think,think.
我在教你怎么\n实践, 实践, 实践
I'm teaching you how to do,do,do.
do-do\nDoo-doo.
（孩童用语“大便”）
对啊
Totally.
我考虑很多
So I think a lot.
因为我恰好有一个\n很聪明的大脑
I happen to have a very powerful brain.
那不可能有用
It can't be helped.
噢, 不, 它可以
Oh,yes,it can.
有趣
Interesting.
Ted, 我相信我们相遇\n是有原因的
Ted,I believe you and I met for a reason.
就象上天在说, 嘿, Barney
It's like the universe was saying,"hey,Barney,
有个家伙 不错的家伙
"there's this dude-- he's pretty cool
但你的工作是让他变的很棒
but it's your job to make him awesome."
你的脑把你给搞砸了, Ted
Your brain screws you up,Ted.
一直这样
It gets in the way.
Robin也是
It happened with Robin,
半个乳房也是
it happened with half boob,
这些事会一直发生\n直到……
and it's gonna keep on \nhappening until you power down
你用酒医治你的神经妄想症
that bucket of neuroses inebriation-style.
那么, 怎么, 你想我喝一杯吗?
So,what,you want me to do a shot?
噢, 不 我想要你把五杯都喝了
Oh,no. I want you to do five shots.
喔 喔 更加有趣了
Ooh.Ooh. More interesting.
Barney, 我觉得你...
Barney,I think you've officially...
不, 别考虑了 喝吧
no,don't think. Do.
Ted, 他是对的 你想太多了
Ted,he's right: You overthink.
也许你应该多喝点
Maybe you should overdrink.
喝, 喝... 喝\n喝, 喝...
Drink,drink... drink,\ndrink,drink... drin drink,drink...
呃, Lily, 你来告诉\n他们这事有多蠢?
uh,Lily,will you tell these \nguys how stupid they're being?
伙计, 你们太不成熟和愚蠢了
Guys,you are being immature and moronic,
……还有喝, 喝... 噢!
……and drink,drink... oh!
喝... 喝...
Drink,drink,ink... drink,drink,drink...
让我来告诉你一点\n关于这大脑的事, 好吗?
Let me tell you something about this brain,okay?
酒精不能让\n这脑袋停止思考
Mere alcohol cannot stop this brain.
喝... 我喜欢这个!
Drink,drink... I love it!
我喜欢这个! 我喜欢这个!
I love it! I love it!
这大脑, 亲爱的凡人们\n这不是普通的大脑
This brain,dear mortals,is no ordinary brain.
喝... 这是超级大脑
Drink,drink... this is a super brain.
是不可能被阻止思考的
this brain is unstoppable.
这大脑...
This brain...
这就是所有我记得的了
and that's all I remember.
除了一些模糊的记忆
Except for a few other hazy memories.
但真的, 下面我记得的
But really,the next thing I remember
就是第二天早晨醒来的事了
was waking up the following morning,
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-\n荣誉出品\n本字幕由cece&飞飞字幕组倾情奉献，仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-\n制作:飞飞\n校对:西西宝贝\n最好的字幕只为献给最亲爱的宝贝
所以就有好多\n亟待解答的问题了
so there were some unanswered questions.
我喝了多少?
How much did I drink?
我怎么弄伤脚踝的?
How did I sprain my ankle?
在我床上的女孩是谁?
Who was this girl in my bed?
我们的摇滚明星来了
There's our rock star.
好吧, 呃... 昨晚\n到底发生了什么?
Okay,uh... what the hell happened last night?
你真的都不记得了吗\n超级大脑?
You really don't remember,superbrain?
Marshall叔叔和Lily阿姨\n补上了我的记忆
So uncle Marshall and aunt Lilly filled me in.
你们觉得这酒怎么样?
And how did you guys like the shots?
我把五杯都喝完了, 婊子
I drank all five,bitch.
我喜欢喝醉的Ted
I love drunk Ted.
Marshall认为你是吸血鬼
Marshall thinks you're vampire.
好吧, 如果他吐了
all right,if he pukes,
你们之一要清理干净
one of you guys cleans it up.
不是我
No dibs.
噢 不是... 该死! 耶
Oh. No D... damn it! Yes.
我忘了你有多快了
How quickly you l forget.
从高中起我就没吐过了
I haven't puked since high school.
我从93年起就没吐过了
I am vomit-free since 93.
93年起, 免吐王\n这太好笑了 我很好笑!
Vomit-free since 93. That's funny.I'm funny!
你在给谁打电话?
Who are you calling?
Robin\nRobin.
噢, 坏主意
Oh,bad idea jeans.
不, 不, 这是个好主意
No,no,it's a great idea.
这就是为什么要喝醉的重点
That's the whole point of getting drunk.
你可以做一些清醒时候\n不可能做的事情
You do things you'd never do if you were sober.
-援引你睡过的女人的话\n-说的好
Says every girl you've ever slept with.Say what?
喂, Robin 我是Ted
Hello,Robin.It's Ted.
噢, 嗨, Ted
Oh,hi,Ted.
你好, Robin 我是Ted
Hello,Robin. It's Ted.
嗨, Ted听起来你兴致很高
Hi,Ted. Sounds like you're having fun.
Robin, 我有告诉过你
Robin,have I ever told you that
我从93年就没吐过?
I am vomit-free since 93?
听着, Ted, 我现在\n不方便聊... 93年?
Listen,Ted,I can't really talk right... 93?
伙计, 这很让人惊讶
Dude,that's impressive.
Robin, 我永远也说不够
Robin,I don't say this enough,
但你确实是个不错的女人\n和伟大的记者
but you're a great woman,and a great reporter.
你应该上“60分钟”\n（CBS著名新闻节目）
You should be on 60 minutes.
你应该是那些分钟的一员
You should be one of the minutes.
这很让人高兴... 和奇怪
That's sweet... and odd.
但我现在正在约会
But I'm kind of on a date right now.
对, 我不同意Barney的观点
Yeah,and I disagree with Barney.
那家伙花了很多钱
Just cause this guy's spending a lot of money
并不代表你得献身
doesn't mean you have to put out.
放慢点进度, Robin
Take it slow,Robin.
放慢点
Take it slow.
慢点... 拜, Ted
Slow... bye,Ted.
-慢点... \n-哇, 对了
Slow... wow,right.
这就是为什么我们不喝
That's why we don't do shots.
朋友不会让朋友\n喝醉然后打电话
Friends don't let friends drink and dial.
我要拿回电话
I need that phone back.
你会在下课的时候拿到的
You'll get this back at the end of class.
叮 下课了\n你的电话, 小朋友
Ding.Class dismissed.Here you go,kid.
你给谁打电话都行
You call whoever you want.
谢谢, 好心的老师
Thank you,kind sir.
至少有人欣赏我
At least someone appreciates the fact that
行动，而不是考虑
I am doing and not thinking.
还有现在, 我不会想
And now,I don't think I won't
我不去厕所
not go to the bathroom.
这有必要吗?
Was that necessary?
他不是在做明智的决定
He is not making smart decisions.
完全正确，就象\n他下一步要做什么?
Exactly.It's like,what's he gonna do next?
我不知道, 但我要找出来
I don't know,but I want to find out.
烂把戏?
cheap trick?
噢, Ted
Oh,Ted.
又见了, Ted
hello again,Ted.
嘿，我又来了
Hey,it's me again
清晰的再次相见
plain to see again
求求你，能不能每天与你见面
please,can I see you every day
我爱这里每个人!
I love everyone in this bar!
我们也爱你,醉Ted!
we love you,drunk Ted!
我又一次成了笨蛋
I'm a fool again
我又落入了爱……
I fell lo... ve.
Ted?\nTed?
嗯, 这就解释了为什么脚踝痛
Well,that explainthe ankle.
后来我们把你带回家睡觉
Then we brought you home and put you to bed.
有别的人和我一起回来吗?
Was there anyone else in there with me?
嘘 有个女的在里面!
Shh.Thers a girl in there!
我知道
I know.
和一个菠萝
And a pineapple.
我知道
I know.
她是谁?
Who is she?
不知道
I don't know.
我的夹克怎么了?
What the hell happened to my jacket?
哇
Whoa.
里面那女的还活着, 是不?
That girl in there is alive,right?
我得给Barney打个电话
I should call Barney.
可能他知道发生什么了
Maybe he knows what happened.
喂
Hello.
你干嘛睡在我们的浴缸里?
Why are you sleeping in our tub?
呃, 陶瓷保持西装不变皱
Uh,the porcelain keeps the suit from wrinkling.
等等, 我昨天半夜上厕所
Wait,were you here when I went to the bathroom
你也在这儿？
in the middle of the night?
别担心
Don't worry.
我睡着了
I slept through it.
事实上我没睡着
I totally didn't sleep through it.
噢, 哇, 你身材这么娇小\n看不出容量这么大
Oh,and wow,for a little girl,you got a big tank.
你到底怎么进来的?
How did you get in here anyway?
我们大概一点钟\n把Ted弄上床的
We put Ted to bed around 1:00.
噢, 你们把Ted弄上床, 好吧
Oh,you put Ted to bed,all right.
你们照顾我
You guys take care of me.
你们是最棒的
You guys are the best.
我爱死你们了
I love you guys so much.
-晚安, Ted \n-我也爱你 伙计
Good night,Ted. Love you,too,buddy.
我又来了, 宝贝!
I'm back,baby doll!
嘿! 嘿! 他又来啦!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! He rallies!
夜生活开始了!
And the night begins now!
好了 精神点\nCarl, 再来两杯
All right.Game face on. Carl,two more.
好吧 这个怎么样?
All right,what do we think of this one?
-我觉得她... \n-圈套问题 不许想
I think she...trick question.No thinking.
你知道几点了吗?
You know what time it is?
哼?
Huh?
是做事时间了
It's do o'clock.
我们走吧
Let's ride.
上吧！
Bring it!
嗨 见过Ted吗?
Hi. Have you met Ted?
抱歉
Excuse me.
你在给Robin打电话吗
You're calling Robin.
我在给Robin打电话
I'm calling Robin.
Ted, 做为你身体上\n和精神上的导师
Ted,as your mentor and spiritual guide,
我禁止你打给她
I forbid you from calling her.
噢, 耶? 你想怎样?
Oh,yeah? What you gonna do?
如果你打电话
If you complete that call,
我就点燃你的外套
I will set your coat on fire.
你在唬我
You're bluffing.
喂, Robin 我是Ted
Hello,Robin. It's Ted.
-Ted, 最后一次, 停止... \n-哇!
-Ted,for the last time,stop...\n-ow!
Ted?\nTed?
你用火烧我
You set me on fire.
真皮不会烧的这么快的
Real suede wouldn't have gone up so fast.
你被抢钱了 这是假的
You got robbed.This is a blend.
你用火烧我
You set me on fire.
我床上那女的是谁?
And who's the girl in my bed?
有个女的在你床上
There's a girl in your bed.
和一个菠萝
And a pineapple.
我是唯一一个对\n菠萝感兴趣的吗?
Am I the only one who's \ncurious about the pineapple?
她是谁?
Who is she?
我不知道
I have no idea.
很好
Nice.
你真不知道那是谁吗?
You really don't know who that is?
不知道 在我用饮料枪
No. After I hosed you down
把你扑灭后
with the beverage gun,
就把你带回来了
I brought you back here.
我希望没有被烧伤
I better not have gotten burned.
啊... 你们谁写了这个吗?
Ah... did any you write that? "
嗨 我是Ted, 如果走失了, 请打...\n这是谁的电话?
Hi. I'm Ted. If lost,please call..." \nwhose number is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
伙计, 打一下吧
Dude,call it.
噢, 等等, 我要去弄点爆米花
Ooh,hold on,I'm gonna make some popcorn.
现在可以打了
You can call now.
天, 这太紧张了 我爱死了
God,this is intense.I love it.
喂?
Hello?
呃... 嗨 你是谁?
Uh... hi. Who's this?
你打过来的 你是谁?
You called me.Who's this?
我是Ted
It's Ted.
我是Carl在酒吧里
It's Carl from the bar.
然后Carl告诉我发生了什么
And then Carl filled us in.
Barney, 你老是照顾我
Barney,you've always taken care of me.
你真是个绅士和学者
You are a gentlemen and a scholar.
去我的马厩牵我最好的马
Go into my stable and take my finest stallion.
他是你的了 他叫追风
He's yours. His name is windjammer.
睡觉吧, 兄弟
Sleep it off,bro.
我回来了, 宝贝! 耶
I'm back,baby doll! Yeah.
我... 我要吐了
And I... am gonna throw up.
我吐了吗? 噢, 我的记录没了
I threw up? Oh,my streak is over.
05年起免吐王\n听起来一点都不棒
Vomit-free since 05 doesn't sound good.
抱歉, Carl 继续
Sorry,Carl. Go on.
Carl... 你知道"卡拉OK"这个词
Carl... did you know the word "karaoke" is
是日语“无人伴奏的乐队”
japanese for "empty orchestra"?
你说这个词是多么\n美丽的萦绕心头
Isn't that hauntingly beautiful?
你是吸血鬼吗?
Are you a vampire?
好吧, 我不会给你酒了
All right,I'm cutting you off.
回家睡觉去, Ted
Go home and get some sleep,Ted.
耶, 太阳很快就要升起来了
Yeah,the sun's gonna come up soon.
不能让我们看见\n你的原形，是不？
Wouldn't want to be around for that,would we?
嘿, 你觉得溜进
Hey,how easy do you think it
动物园容易吗?
would be to sneak into the zoo?
我想看企鹅, 就现在
I have to see some penguins,like,right now.
好了, 把胳膊给我
All right,give me your arm.
好的
Okay.
这样, 如果你醉倒在水沟里了
This way,if you pass out in the gutter \nIt tickles.
...有人会给我打电话
...Someone will call me,
我会去找你
and I will come get you.
谢谢你, Carl
Thanks,Carl.
我们不能只做朋友
We can't just be friends.
我们互相吸引
We're attracted to each other,
我们都清楚
and we both know it.
什么?
Excuse me?
Robin和我, Robin和我
Me and Robin,me and Robin.
我得再打个电话
I have to make one more call.
对, 这次会不错的
Yeah,this'll go good.
嘿, 又是我
hey,it's me again.
听着, 谁在开玩笑?
Look,who are we kidding?
我们两个互相吸引
You and I are both attracted to each other.
我们年轻, 我们都醉了\n……我们之一醉了
We-we're young,we're drunk-- half of us
不管怎样 生活只有一辈子
anyway-- and we only get one life.
所以, 为什么你现在\n不马上来我公寓呢
So,why don't you come \nover to my apartment right now,
我们会找点蠢事来做?
and we'll think of \nsomething stupid to do together?
真的吗?
Really?
太好了 等等 真的吗?
Great. Wait. Really?
太好了
Great.
谢谢你, Carl
Thanks,Carl.
是Robin
It's Robin.
里面的是Robin
That's Robin in there.
你们俩有没有...?
Did you guys...?
噢, 拜托
Oh,come on.
怎么说你也一定要\n和我来一下
You've got to give me this one.
那五杯酒让你和\nRobin进展神速
Those five shots got you further with
这是你的脑袋永远做不到的
Robin than your brain ever did.
看你什么也不想的时候\n发生了什么?
See what happens when you don't think?
你做了! 更重要的是\n你“做”了Robin
You do. More importantly,you do Robin.
来吧
Come on.
好吧, 这里
All right,right over here.
但, 呃, 这表示什么?
but,uh,still,what does this mean?
我们要约会了吗?
Are we dating now?
我是说, 我从来没想过\n事情会发展成这样
I-I mean,I never pictured it going down this way,
但是可能这就是\n事情该发展的方向
But maybe that's how it had to happen.
我是说, 想想...
I mean,think about it...
有没有人给他拿点酒\n他又开始考虑了
Someone get him a shot.He's thinking again.
你知道吗?
You know what? Hold on,man.
想想这个问题也不是那么糟
Maybe it's not such a bad idea to think about this one.
你和Robin以前曾经历过
You and Robin went down this road before.
你们处理的相当糟糕
You got dinged up really bad.
你知道谁会想说下
You know who might have something
关于Ted和Robin的未来 ?
to say about Ted's future with Robin?
Robin 去叫醒她
Robin. Go wake her up.
叫醒她然后说什么?
Wake her up and say what?
爹地回家了
Daddy's home.
祝你好运, 伙计
Good luck,buddy.
喂
hello.
Ted, 我是Robin
Ted,it's Robin.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
嘿, Robin, 你怎么样?
hey,Robin,how are you?
Ted, 我觉得我们得谈谈
Ted,I think you and I should have a
昨晚的那些电话
talk about those phone calls last night.
你不介意我现在过去吧?
Do you mind if I swing by?
问问她知道菠萝不
Ask her about the pineapple.
呃, 好, 当然, 过来吧
Uh,yeah,sure,come on over.
谢谢
Thanks.
别 等等, 别来... 她要来了
No. Wait,d-d-don't come... she's coming over.
糟糕！
Crap!
等等 这真要我命
Wait. This is killing me.
我们得弄清楚那女的是谁
We have to find out who that girl is.
Trudy 我叫Trudy
Trudy. My name is Trudy.
后来, Trudy告诉我了后面的事
And then,Trudy filled us in.
我很吃惊为什么\n你没马上甩掉他
I'm just surpris you didn't dump him sooner.
我知道
I know.
那是我永远也找不回的两年
It's two years of my life I'm never getting back.
我的一部分希望我跳上
A little part of me wants to just jump
下一个见到的家伙
the bones of the next guy I see.
爹地回家了
daddy's home.
或者再后面一个
Or the one after that.
好吧, 很公平
Okay,fair enough.
我要向我朋友\n证明一点, 所以
I've got to prove a point to a friend,so,
你已经给了我电话...\n你的名字是Amy 女士们
you just gave me your number... \nand your name is Amy.Ladies.
我爱这里的每个人!
I love everyone in this bar!
看那个傻家伙
look at that idiot go.
他很可爱
He kind of cute.
你在男厕所干嘛?
What are you doing in the men's room?
我在女厕所干嘛?
What am I doing in the ladies' room?
好吧, 我进来是因为
All right,I came in here,cause
我以为我要吐了
I thought I was gonna throw up.
你吐了?
Did you?
我没有
I did not.
记录仍然保持\n93年起免吐王
And the streak continues-- vomit-free since 93.
抱歉, Trudy 继续
I'm sorry,Trudy.Go on.
我喜欢你的表演
I liked your performance.
什么, 那个卡拉OK?
What,the karaoke?
谢谢（日语）
Domo arigato.
我希望我能有你那么勇敢
I wish I had your guts.
站起来，释放自己的白痴状态
Getting up and making a complete idiot of myself.
那么, 做吧
So,do it.
我不知道
I don't know.
当然，我这个星期\n过的很不舒心
Still,I've had a pretty serious week.
我可以找点蠢事做做
I could sure stand to do something stupid.
我就很蠢，做我吧
I'm something stupid. Do me.
你很幽默
You're funny.
嘿, 我能给你打电话吗?
Hey,can I call you sometime?
好的
Okay.
哈, 哈
Ha,ha.
这儿, 我来吧
Here,let me.
为什么他们要起名\n卡拉OK呢?
Why do they call it kaoke,anyhow?
是被一个叫Carrie Oke的\n女人发明的吗?
Was it invented by a woman named Carrie Oke
我就爱想些这类事情
these are the kinds of things I think about.
"卡拉OK"是日语\n“无人伴奏的乐队”
Karaoke is japanese for "empty orchestra" .
哇哦，这是多么美丽\n萦绕心头
Wow. That's hauntingly beautiful.
嘿, 打通了
Hey,it works.
我猜你会给我打电话
Then I guess you're gonna have to call me.
我得再打个电话
I got to make one more call.
喂?
Hello?
-嘿, 又是我\n-嘿
Hey,it's me again. Hey.
听着, 谁在开玩笑?
Look,who are we kidding?
我们俩互相吸引
You and I are both attracted to each other.
我们年轻, 我们醉了\n……我们之一喝醉了
We're-we're young,we're drunk-- half of us,
生活只有一辈子
anyway-- and we only get one life.
所以, 我到这来了
So,I came over here.
现在, 我真的, 真的很尴尬
And now,I'm really,really embarrassed.
该死, Trudy!
Damn it,Trudy!
菠萝是怎么回事?
What about the pineapple?
抱歉 抱歉 抱歉!
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry!
啊, Robin来了
ah,Robin's here.
呃, 听着, Trudy\n我需要你藏在卧室
Um,look,Trudy,I need you to hide in my bedroom.
为什么? 是你女朋友吗?
Why? Is that your girlfriend?
啊, 不, 那不是我女朋友
Ah,no,that's not my girlfriend.
呃, 听着, 这很复杂
Um,look,it's complicated.
噢, 你结婚了, 耶, 我知道\n我不敢相信我这么做了
Oh,you're married.\nYeah,I know.I can't believe I did this.
不, 不, 不, 我没结婚
No,no,no,I-I'm not married.
呃... 你藏起来后我会解释
Um... I'll explain after you hide.
嘿 嗨, 伙计们
Hey. Hi,guys.
嘿, Robin, 早上好\n嗨
Hey,Robin,top of the morning.Hi.
嗨, Robin 不错的毛衣
Hi,Robin.Good sweater.
呃, 抱歉我一直\n那样给你打电话
Um,sorry I kept calling you like that.
我太醉了
I was pretty drunk.
呃, 别开玩笑了
Uh,no kidding.
那些电话太奇怪了
Those calls were really weird.
听着, Ted, 也许我们该谈谈
Look,Ted,maybe we need to talk.
我们去吃点东西
Let's go get a snack.
我喜欢吃东西
I love to snack.
我不用了
I'm good.
拜托, 那些电话没那么怪
Come on,those calls weren't that weird.
Robin! 出来!
Robin! Come hang out!
好吧, 我要继续发出\n这种声音直到你出来
Okay,I'm gonna make \nthis sound till you come hang out.
啊....
Aaah....
这持续了三分半钟
that goes on for three and a half minutes.
没有换气吗?
Without a breath?
这应该可以成世界纪录了
That's got to be some kind of record.
噢, Ted, 你不能这样
Oh,Ted,you can't do this.
求你了 我们答应了做朋友
Please.We agreed to be friends,
但现在你把一切都弄乱了
and now you're making it all confusing.
不, 我没有
No,I'm not.
听着, 我只是让我的大脑\n休息了一晚
Look,I-I just turned off my brain for the night.
没有什么改变了
Nothing's changed.
你继续过你的 我继续过我的
You've moved on.I've moved on.
你真的没想了吗?
Really,you've moved on?
是啊 什么, 你不相信我吗?
Yes. What,you don't believe me?
噢 呃, 好吧
oh. Uh,okay.
Trudy, 出来吧
Trudy,come on out.
你会笑出来的
You are gonna laugh.
等等 你昨晚和某人在一起?
Wait. You were with someone last night?
是啊, Trudy 她不错
Yeah,Trudy. She's cool.
Trudy, 出来吧
Trudy,come on out.
是啊, 真的, 没什么
Yeah,seriously,it's okay.
这就是Trudy\n她很害羞... 我觉得...
This is so Trudy.\nShe's really shy... I think...
Trudy?\nTrudy?
嗨, Trudy 我是Robin
Hi,Trudy.I'm Robin.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
你是对的，她很害羞
She is shy.
我不是编的
I'm not making this up.
她一定从安全通道爬下去了
She-she must have climbed out the fire escape.
不管怎样 不管怎样!
whatever. Whatever!
我不在乎你怎么想
I-I don't care what you think.
那为什么你把她藏起来躲我?
Then why'd you hide her from me?
哇 你很聪明
Wow. You're good.
有没人告诉你\n你应该上60 minutes?
Anyone ever tell you you should be on 60 minutes?
是的 你说过... 昨晚
Yes. You did... last night.
真的？
Really.uh...
睡一下吧, Ted
get some sleep,Ted.
你过了个漫长的夜晚
You had a long night.
别觉得糟糕
And don't feel bad.
我有过更糟的
I've woken up with worse.
我给Trudy留了言
I left Trudy a message,
但她一直没有回电给我
but she never called me back.
有些时候这就是生活
That's just how life works sometimes.
你关掉大脑一晚
You turn off your brain for a night,
第二天你剩下的就是
and all your left with
就是糟糕的宿醉
the next day is a bad hangover,
扭伤的脚踝,和一个菠萝
a sprained ankle,and a pineapple.
噢, 我们也一直不知道
Oh,we never found out
那个菠萝是哪来的
where that pineapple came from,
但是它很可口
but it was delicious.